- +971 50 240 6010
- ĭihan\_alsayed9310@icloud.com
- Sharjah, Uae

# Jehan Alsayed

Sales



#### SUMMARY

Experienced sales professional with 7 years in the industry seeking to use customer service and communication skills to maintain client relationships and establish new ones through leads and cold calls to maintain a consistent success rate.

This experienced professional will go the extra mile making cold calls to push sales, an uncommon talent that this applicant has past success with.

# SKILLS

Word

Excel

**PowerPoint** 

# LANGUAGES

en

ar

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### sales

kashakha

05/2019 - 11/2021

Re-organized something to make it work better

Identified a problem and solved it

Come up with a new idea that improved things

Developed or implemented new procedures or systems

#### sales

qasr alhayam

02/2018 - 02/2019

Perfumes and abayas

Revenue or sales you increased for the company.

Money you saved for the company.

Time you saved for the company.

Problems you identified and solved.

Ideas or innovations you introduced.

Procedures or systems you developed, implemented, or optimized.

## Sales

Monsieur Ghanem

02/2014 - 04/2017

## EDUCATION

Zagazig Center

2016

Diploma commercial technician